KANNIKA KHONGPAN

Software Engineer

Bangplat, Bangkok, Thailand.

<u>@</u>

kkannika.github.io



(+66) 65 989 7887



I have extensive experience in technical services support and the educational system. My passion for software development began after I received a Working and Holiday visa in Australia and was stuck in the city due to the Covid-19 situation, which inspired me to attend the online coding Bootcamp. My first coding class taught me that software development perfectly balances analytical thinking, problem-solving, and creative exploration. I can apply everything that I have learned and looking forward to developing more intuitive tools as a software engineer.

Experience

Overseas Procurement Analyst – PSD Color Way

Jun 2021 - Dec 2021

- Communicated between the overseas suppliers, planned to order and followed order confirmation, delivery schedule, and shipping document.
- Coordinated with the shipping agent, Inland Freight, Sea Freight, Air Freight.
- Made a report such as a summary of order and order status.

Technical Services Assistant – Tetra Pak (Thailand)

Mar 2018 - Aug 2020

- Administrative supported to Technical Services Department
- Prepared relevant material for the workshops Managed sample requests
- Made translations of presentations when required Maintained Directors's calendar ie. Planned meetings, teleconferences, and travel.

English Language Teacher – Ratchaborika Nukroh School

Mar 2017 - Mar 2018

- Handled English classes for Grades 10-12
- Planned well-rounded lessons that encouraged students to think creatively
- Served as a homeroom advisor to 45 students

Education

Software Engineering Bootcamp – Codestar

Mar 2022 - Apr 2022

A coding bootcamp with Java and Javascript-based curriculum that concentrates on developing proficiency in technologies.

Bachelor of Art in English – Suan Sunandha Rajabhat University

May 2012 - Sep 2016

Projects

My personal website

- kkannika.github.io

Personal website on GitHub domain including my portfolio and projects which are made by Javascript, HTML and CSS.

Certifications

The Complete 2022 Web Development Bootcamp

London App Brewery (Udemy)

IBM Full Stack Cloud Developer

- IBM (Coursera)

Google IT Support Specialization

- Google (Coursera)

Languages

Thai – Native Proficiency

English – Professional Working Proficiency

with Upper Intermediate level

(Certificate available upon request)

Skills

Java Jav

Javascript

HTML5

CSS3

Spring Boot

Maven

Express

React

Node

MySQL

, ,

MongoDB

GitHub